var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "the one who",
        "pcklId": "1437",
        "rootWordId": 59,
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": 1464,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " أَرَأَيْتَ الَّذِي يُكَذِّبُ بِالدِّينِ",
        "rootWord": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "waznEnglish": "who, which, that",
        "waznTlit": "alladhī",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Relative pronoun)",
        "waznFreq": 1464,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the one who",
        "pcklId": "1438",
        "rootWordId": 59,
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": 1464,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَذَٰلِكَ الَّذِي يَدُعُّ الْيَتِيمَ",
        "rootWord": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "waznEnglish": "who, which, that",
        "waznTlit": "alladhī",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Relative pronoun)",
        "waznFreq": 1464,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1439",
        "rootWordId": 59,
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": 1464,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِينَ هُمْ عَنْ صَلَاتِهِمْ سَاهُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "waznEnglish": "who, which, that",
        "waznTlit": "alladhī",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Relative pronoun)",
        "waznFreq": 1464,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "Those who",
        "pcklId": "1440",
        "rootWordId": 59,
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": 1464,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِينَ هُمْ يُرَاءُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "ٱلَّذِى",
        "waznEnglish": "who, which, that",
        "waznTlit": "alladhī",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Relative pronoun)",
        "waznFreq": 1464,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَحُضُّ",
        "answer": "feel the urge",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 331,
        "tlit": "yaḥuḍḍu",
        "frequency": 3,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا يَحُضُّ عَلَىٰ طَعَامِ الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ح ض ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَحُضُّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to feel the urge",
        "waznTlit": "yaḥuḍḍu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدُعُّ",
        "answer": "repulses",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 473,
        "tlit": "yaduʿʿu",
        "frequency": 3,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَذَٰلِكَ الَّذِي يَدُعُّ الْيَتِيمَ",
        "rootWord": "د ع ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَدُعُّ",
        "waznEnglish": "to thrust, to repulse",
        "waznTlit": "yaduʿʿu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالدِّينِ",
        "answer": "the Judgment",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "rootWordId": 498,
        "tlit": "bil-dīni",
        "frequency": 101,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " أَرَأَيْتَ الَّذِي يُكَذِّبُ بِالدِّينِ",
        "rootWord": "د ي ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "دِين",
        "waznEnglish": "they acknowledge",
        "waznTlit": "dīn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 92,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرَأَيْتَ",
        "answer": "Have you seen",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "ara-ayta",
        "frequency": 328,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " أَرَأَيْتَ الَّذِي يُكَذِّبُ بِالدِّينِ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَءَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "raā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرَاءُونَ",
        "answer": "make show",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "yurāūna",
        "frequency": 328,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِينَ هُمْ يُرَاءُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يُرَآءُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to show off",
        "waznTlit": "yurāu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form III)",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "answer": "the poor",
        "pcklId": "65",
        "rootWordId": 708,
        "tlit": "l-mis'kīni",
        "frequency": 69,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا يَحُضُّ عَلَىٰ طَعَامِ الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "rootWord": "س ك ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مِسْكِين",
        "waznEnglish": "Dwell",
        "waznTlit": "mis'kīn",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 23,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "سَاهُونَ",
        "answer": "(are) neglectful",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 736,
        "tlit": "sāhūna",
        "frequency": 2,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِينَ هُمْ عَنْ صَلَاتِهِمْ سَاهُونَ",
        "rootWord": "س ه و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "س ه و",
        "waznEnglish": "(of) heedlessness",
        "waznTlit": "sīn hā wāw",
        "waznType": "Active participle",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "صَلَاتِهِمْ",
        "answer": "their prayers",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "rootWordId": 857,
        "tlit": "ṣalātihim",
        "frequency": 99,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " الَّذِينَ هُمْ عَنْ صَلَاتِهِمْ سَاهُونَ",
        "rootWord": "ص ل و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "صَلَوٰة",
        "waznEnglish": "praying",
        "waznTlit": "ṣalat",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 83,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْمُصَلِّينَ",
        "answer": "to those who pray",
        "pcklId": "98",
        "rootWordId": 857,
        "tlit": "lil'muṣallīna",
        "frequency": 99,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَوَيْلٌ لِلْمُصَلِّينَ",
        "rootWord": "ص ل و",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مُصَلِّين",
        "waznEnglish": "praying",
        "waznTlit": "muṣallīn",
        "waznType": "Active participle (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "طَعَامِ",
        "answer": "feed",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "rootWordId": 911,
        "tlit": "ṭaʿāmi",
        "frequency": 48,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَلَا يَحُضُّ عَلَىٰ طَعَامِ الْمِسْكِينِ",
        "rootWord": "ط ع م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "طَعَام",
        "waznEnglish": "taste it",
        "waznTlit": "ṭaʿām",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 24,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يُكَذِّبُ",
        "answer": "denies",
        "pcklId": "186",
        "rootWordId": 1263,
        "tlit": "yukadhibu",
        "frequency": 282,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " أَرَأَيْتَ الَّذِي يُكَذِّبُ بِالدِّينِ",
        "rootWord": "ك ذ ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "كَذَّبَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to deny, to reject",
        "waznTlit": "kadhaba",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 176,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَاعُونَ",
        "answer": "[the] small kindnesses",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 1405,
        "tlit": "l-māʿūna",
        "frequency": 1,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَمْنَعُونَ الْمَاعُونَ",
        "rootWord": "م ع ن",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "م ع ن",
        "waznEnglish": "[the] small kindnesses",
        "waznTlit": "mīm ʿayn nūn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيَمْنَعُونَ",
        "answer": "And they deny",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "rootWordId": 1418,
        "tlit": "wayamnaʿūna",
        "frequency": 17,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَيَمْنَعُونَ الْمَاعُونَ",
        "rootWord": "م ن ع",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مَّنَعَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to prevent",
        "waznTlit": "manaʿa",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 12,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْيَتِيمَ",
        "answer": "the orphan",
        "pcklId": "20",
        "rootWordId": 1656,
        "tlit": "l-yatīma",
        "frequency": 23,
        "surahnum": 107,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَذَٰلِكَ الَّذِي يَدُعُّ الْيَتِيمَ",
        "rootWord": "ي ت م",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ي ت م",
        "waznEnglish": "and [the] orphans",
        "waznTlit": "yā tā mīm",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 23,
        "hasRootWord": true
    }
]; 
export default words;